which he which he willingly does I think
one of the things that you said earlier
and this is really really true you have
to have something to hang these pictures
online yeah you have to get in the word
you're not gonna discover anything if
you're not spending time in the word so
even if you don't know how to study yet
start reading the words because you
begin to pick this and this and put it
together the Holy Spirit will well show
you how together yeah
like fill your mind right I love
listening your story our kid stories but
guess what you listen those stories and
you're like and then what happened like
that's one of the that's a very powerful
way to hang these pictures and memories
all right so whatever you need to do if
it's listen the Bible stories just start
throwing those stories in there you
don't have to make sense of it now put
them in there and you begin to see you
begin when when you train your mind how
to begin to think in pictures mm-hmm
like it just comes to life in an amazing
way in an amazing way so touch on the
the daniel statue you know i want you to
get to that so this is an example of
learning how to think in pictures all
right this is a paradigm shift if you
will and let me say this I like to say
this God has given every one of us a
camera and it's this right here mm-hmm
now you know some of us have old cameras
and I don't mean age I mean you remember
how you know you used to have to develop
a picture in the old days no it took
like hours and hours yes some of us have
those kind of cameras right and others
of us have like iPhones and you know
sand read something and you're like boom
I see that right and so if you have an
old camera don't be discouraged right
because the more you train your mind
to think photo Theology to think in
pictures to think in dimensions the
easier it's going to become you'll be
reading a text and you will just see
that text becomes living because and you
guys have seen it on the set of you know
yeah
salvation salvation symbols yeah you
know James and I are talking in while
he's talking or while I'm talking one of
us is like oh please stop mm-hmm we just
read no everyone's no look at this and
all of a sudden we all see something
that we had not seen before yeah that's
what we want we want to learn we want to
see this Bible the text begin to just
pop off the page yeah we're moving and
it's moving yeah yeah it becomes not 3d
but 5d yeah and so I'm using the exact
I'm not even going to use that example
because we will get in trouble so
different example when you practice
anything you learn different techniques
right but really the art of that I am
gonna use this example and just just
forgive me for using it but I was a
martial artist back in the day okay and
as a martial artist you study technique
right you have different forms so you
study this form you say this form you
study this form for the purpose of when
you get into a fight you're not going
through you know okay this form right
now this for know you're taking bits and
pieces from each form to adapt to that
particular situation mm-hmm right in the
very same way Bible study is learning
how to take pieces of the different
techniques and bringing it together to
handle a text that you're fighting with
with this text man how do i how do I get
how do I break into an understanding of
this text and so you're learning to use
these different principles of followed
theology dimensions the connection game
and there are other principles that
you're like okay now I'm seeing how this
works and soon you begin to learn how do
you like all of these things we
to bear on the text and you're not
thinking okay now let me think in five
dimensions it becomes fluid to you
it becomes reflexive that's what they
did in the martial arts you practice a
form so much on that when you got into a
fight it was like okay I'm responding
without even it's just reflexive yeah
that's what we want on a spiritual level
don't anyone right into 3abn muscle
memory muscle memory so